Now, let's look at the second metric which is Recall.
现在看看第二个指标 即召回率
召回率可以回答以下问题
Recall is the answer to the following question.
在所有标记为阳性的点中
Out of the points that are labeled positive,
how many of them were correctly predicted as positive?
有哪些正确地预测为阳性？
在医疗模型中 召回率可以回答以下问题
So in the medical model, recall is the answer to the following question.
Out of the sick patients,
在生病患者当中
有多少位正确地诊断为生病了？
how many did we correctly diagnosed as sick?
So remember, precision was out of the patients who were diagnosed as sick,
精度是诊断为生病的患者当中
有多少位真正生病了？
how many were actually sick?
但召回率刚好相反
But recall is the opposite.
在生病的患者当中
Out of the patients are sick,
有多少位正确地诊断为生病了？
how many did we correctly diagnosed as sick?
可以看做算法的覆盖范围
It can be seen as a reach of the algorithm.
How many of the positive points did I manage to catch?
我能够发现多少阳性点
答案用这行计算
The answer is calculated with this row.
可以看出 这行发现了用 X 表示的重要情形
And as we can see, this row catches a critical case labelled
可以看出在医疗模型中召回率很重要
by an X so we can see that recall is important in the medical model.
要计算召回率 我们执行以下操作
Now to calculate recall, we do the following.
在 1200 位生病患者当中
From a 1200 sick patients,
我们正确地诊断了多少位？
how many did we diagnose correctly?
也就是 1000/1200 等于 83.3%
That's a thousand divided by 1200 which is 83.3%.
This model better have a high recall because we're trying to
这个模型最好具有很高的召回率 因为我们尝试
尽可能发现很多的生病患者
correctly catch as many of the sick people as possible.
Now in the e-mail model,
在电子邮件模型中
recall is defined similarly.
召回率的定义比较相似
计算方式如下
It is calculated as follows.
From the spam emails,
在垃圾邮件中
how many of them did we correctly send to the spam folder?
有多少封正确地发送到了垃圾文件夹？
The answer is in this row over here,
答案是这行
so we have a hundred correctly sent to the spam folder divided by 270 total spam emails.
也就是 100 封正确地发送到垃圾文件夹的邮件除以共 270 封垃圾邮件
数字更小 为 37%
It's a low number. It's 37%.
但是我们关心的是避免这个 X
But remember, we are worried about avoiding this X over here.
Since we don't mind if we don't catch
因为我们并不介意没有发现所有的垃圾邮件
all the spam emails as long as the ones we caught are spam.
只要发现的垃圾邮件的确是垃圾邮件即可
So it's okay that this model has a low recall.
因此这个模型可以具有很低的召回率
Now let's do a similar exercise as before.
我们再做道类似的练习
In this linear model over here,
在此线性模型中
what is the recall?
召回率是多少？
Enter your answer below.
请将答案填在下方